{
  "quiz": [
    {
      "category": "Java Programming",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Identify the keyword used to define a class in Java.",
      "answer": "class"
    },
    {
      "category": "Trivia",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Identify the smallest country in the world by land area.",
      "answer": "Vatican City"
    },
    {
      "category": "Basic English",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Identify the part of speech of the word 'quickly'.",
      "answer": "Adverb"
    },
    {
      "category": "Theory",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Identify the concept in quantum mechanics that describes the wave-particle duality.",
      "answer": "De Broglie hypothesis"
    },
    {
      "category": "Basic English",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Identify the correct plural form of 'child'.",
      "answer": "Children"
    },
    {
      "category": "Trivia",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Identify the year when the first man landed on the moon.",
      "answer": "1969"
    },
    {
      "category": "Java Programming",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Identify the design pattern which decouples an abstraction from its implementation in Java.",
      "answer": "Bridge pattern"
    },
    {
      "category": "Basic English",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Identify the synonym of 'happy' in Basic English.",
      "answer": "Glad"
    },
    {
      "category": "Theory",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Identify the scientific theory that explains the origin of the universe.",
      "answer": "Big Bang Theory"
    },
    {
      "category": "Trivia",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Identify the actor who played the role of The Joker in the 2008 film 'The Dark Knight'.",
      "answer": "Heath Ledger"
    },
    {
      "category": "Filipino Trivia",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Identify the national flower of the Philippines.",
      "answer": "Sampaguita"
    },
    {
      "category": "Filipino Trivia",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Identify the official language of the Philippines.",
      "answer": "Filipino"
    },
    {
      "category": "Filipino Trivia",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Identify the historical event that signaled the start of the Philippine Revolution against Spain.",
      "answer": "Cry of Pugad Lawin"
    },
    {
      "category": "Filipino Trivia",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Identify the highest mountain in the Philippines.",
      "answer": "Mount Apo"
    },
    {
      "category": "Filipino Trivia",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Identify the capital city of the Philippines.",
      "answer": "Manila"
    }
  ],
  "points": [
    {
      "student": "Alice",
      "points": 80
    },
    {
      "student": "Bob",
      "points": 90
    }
  ]
}
